<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><!DOCTYPE tmc-service-paragraph SYSTEM "../dtd/paragraph-contents.dtd">
<tmc-service-paragraph><pub id="RM25T0E"><servcat id="_57"><name>Power Source / Network</name><section id="_057931"><name>NETWORKING</name><ttl id="_0556385"><name>CAN COMMUNICATION SYSTEM(w/ Pre-collision System)</name><para category="Y" id="RM1000000025U8F"><dtccode/><dtcname>HOW TO PROCEED WITH TROUBLESHOOTING</dtcname><subpara category="10" id="RM1000000025U8F_02"><name>CAUTION / NOTICE / HINT</name><content5><step1><ptxt>PRECAUTIONS WHEN TROUBLESHOOTING</ptxt><atten3><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>Because the order of diagnosis is important to allow correct diagnosis, make sure to begin troubleshooting using How to Proceed with Troubleshooting when CAN communication system related DTCs are output.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If the CAN communication system is malfunctioning, check the contact pressure of the terminals in the connectors, as insufficient terminal contact pressure may be the cause.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM100000000G4HS" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="001"/></mlink></ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Before measuring the resistance of the CAN bus, turn the ignition switch off and leave the vehicle for 1 minute or more without operating the key or any switches, or opening or closing the doors. After that, disconnect the cable from the negative (-) battery terminal and leave the vehicle for 1 minute or more before measuring the resistance.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>When disconnecting and reconnecting the battery.</ptxt><atten4><ptxt>When disconnecting and reconnecting the battery, there is an automatic learning function that completes learning when the respective system is used.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM1000000024VLU" label="Seep00002" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></atten4></item><item><ptxt>Some parts must be initialized and set when replacing or removing and installing parts.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM1000000024VNU" label="Seep00003" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></item></list1></atten3><step2><ptxt>CAN communication DTCs are output for CAN main bus and CAN branch malfunctions as well as for internal malfunctions or power source malfunctions of ECUs or sensors for systems using CAN communication. Therefore, when DTCs for internal malfunctions or power source malfunctions of corresponding systems are output at the same time as CAN communication DTCs, troubleshoot according to the internal malfunction and power source malfunction DTCs.</ptxt></step2><step2><ptxt>The DLC3 inspection can only be used to detect malfunctions in the diagnosis bus (the bus which connects the DLC3 to the central gateway ECU (network gateway ECU)).</ptxt></step2><step2><ptxt>An open in a branch for ECUs or sensors that are connected to the CAN main bus can be checked by performing a CAN bus check using the GTS. (This inspection is possible when all the main bus lines are normal.)</ptxt></step2><step2><ptxt>If a sub bus has a communication error, the gateway function equipped ECU (sub bus monitor ECU) detects it and stores DTCs related to the error.</ptxt><atten4><ptxt>On the GTS, gateway function equipped ECUs display DTCs for ECUs connected to the sub bus.</ptxt></atten4></step2><step2><ptxt>When an open circuit is detected, before disconnecting related connectors for inspection, push in on the connector body to check that the connector is not loose or disconnected.</ptxt></step2><step2><ptxt>When a connector is disconnected, check that the terminals and connector body are not cracked, deformed or corroded.</ptxt></step2></step1></content5></subpara><subpara category="01" id="RM1000000025U8F_01"><name>PROCEDURE</name><testgrp cellposition="1-1" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0001"><testtitle>VEHICLE BROUGHT TO WORKSHOP</testtitle><content6><atten4><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>If the ignition switch can be turned to ON (the power source mode can be changed to on) when the vehicle is brought in for repair, check for DTCs and check the illumination condition of the indicators in the combination meter assembly and the basic operation of the vehicle (such as steering operation) promptly.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Do not turn the ignition switch off until the inspection of the vehicle is finished, as some fail-safe functions are canceled when the ignition switch is turned off.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If the ignition switch cannot be turned to ON (the power source mode cannot be changed to on) even though the battery voltage is normal, repair this malfunction before performing troubleshooting.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>When the ignition switch cannot be turned to ON, data can be read from ECUs that can communicate with the ignition switch off by connecting the GTS to the vehicle and turning a courtesy light switch on and off at intervals of 1.5 seconds or less until communication starts.</ptxt></item></list1></atten4><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="1"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="4.13in"/><thead><row><entry align="center"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="center"><judge-value label="1"><ptxt>NEXT</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="1-1" label="1"><action actiontype="next" cellposition="2-1" childid="RM1000000025U8F_01_0002"/></result></results></testgrp><testgrp cellposition="2-1" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0002"><testtitle>CUSTOMER PROBLEM ANALYSIS</testtitle><content6><atten4><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>When troubleshooting, confirm that the problem symptoms have been accurately identified. Preconceptions should be discarded in order to make an accurate judgment. To clearly understand what the problem symptoms are, it is extremely important to ask the customer about the problem and the conditions at the time the malfunction occurred.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Ask the customer if the vehicle is/was equipped with additional devices such as a theft deterrent device or monitor. (If equipped, explain to the customer that the additional devices will be removed before performing troubleshooting as the malfunction cannot be checked properly.)</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Examples of points to be confirmed are shown below.</ptxt></item></list1></atten4><test1><ptxt>It is useful to confirm the symptoms and the conditions in which the vehicle was operating at the time when a malfunction occurred. This helps to narrow down the malfunctioning part.</ptxt><atten4><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>What was affected (system, part or meter warning indicators)</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>What happened (details of the malfunction)</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>When (occurrence date and time, frequency and if it recurs or not)</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Under what kind of situation did the problem occur (driving and operating condition at the occurrence and weather)</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Road type or condition (city, suburb, paved road, unpaved road, highway, etc.)</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Conditions when vehicle returned to normal (ignition switch was turned off, etc.)</ptxt></item></list1></atten4><table pgwide="1"><title>Points to be confirmed</title><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="COL1" colwidth="1.42in"/><colspec colname="COL2" colwidth="5.66in"/><tbody><row><entry valign="middle"><ptxt>Symptom</ptxt></entry><entry><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>Air conditioning</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the air conditioning system operated</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the blower fan operated</ptxt><ptxt>- The air conditioning functions cannot be operated at all</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Electric power steering</ptxt><ptxt>- Normal</ptxt><ptxt>- A little heavier than usual</ptxt><ptxt>- There was no assist</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Drive monitor display</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the update of multi-information display items stopped</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the numeric part of the drivable distance was displayed</ptxt><ptxt>- Not displayed at all</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Eco navigation (eco drive) display</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the average fuel consumption graph is updated every minute</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the updated section average fuel consumption graph is displayed</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the distance-to-empty is displayed on the section average fuel consumption graph display</ptxt><ptxt>- Not displayed at all</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Interior lights</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the interior light illumination changes when the door is opened or closed</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the interior lights turned off when the ignition switch is turned to ON</ptxt><ptxt>- Not illuminated at all</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Wireless door lock function and smart entry function</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the lock/unlock function operated</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the entry warning function operated</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the illumination was turned on when the key was brought into a smart detection area</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>4WD/AWD operation</ptxt><ptxt>- Normal</ptxt><ptxt>- Slip detected when starting off</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Memory call</ptxt><ptxt>- Normal</ptxt><ptxt>- Memory write error</ptxt><ptxt>- Memory read error</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the auto return or auto away control is performed</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Operation of other systems of concern</ptxt></item></list1></entry></row><row><entry valign="middle"><ptxt>Meter warning lights</ptxt></entry><entry><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>Illumination of warning lights and the order in which they illuminated</ptxt><ptxt>- Master</ptxt><ptxt>- Check engine (MIL)</ptxt><ptxt>- Brake</ptxt><ptxt>- ABS</ptxt><ptxt>- Slip</ptxt><ptxt>- EPS</ptxt><ptxt>- SRS</ptxt><ptxt>- Others</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Meter display</ptxt><ptxt>- Speedometer</ptxt><ptxt>- Tachometer</ptxt><ptxt>- Engine coolant temperature gauge</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Content displayed on the multi-information display</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the odometer to TRIP meter has stopped</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether the value of the average fuel economy is displayed on the multi-information display</ptxt><ptxt>- Whether a warning message is displayed on the multi-information display</ptxt></item></list1></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></test1><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="1"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="4.13in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="1"><ptxt>NEXT</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="2-1" label="1"><action actiontype="next" cellposition="3-1" childid="RM1000000025U8F_01_0105"/></result></results></testgrp><testgrp cellposition="3-1" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0105"><testtitle>PRE-CHECK</testtitle><content6><test1><ptxt>Measure the battery voltage.</ptxt><spec type="other"><title>Standard voltage</title><specitem><ptxt>11 to 14 V</ptxt></specitem></spec><ptxt>If the voltage is below 11 V, recharge or replace the battery before proceeding to the next step.</ptxt><atten4><ptxt>If the ignition switch cannot be turned to ON, measure the voltage of the battery. If it is below 11 V, perform inspection after replacing or recharging the battery.</ptxt></atten4></test1><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="1"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="4.13in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="1"><ptxt>OK</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="2"><ptxt>NG</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="3-1" label="1"><action actiontype="next" cellposition="4-1" childid="RM1000000025U8F_01_0003"/></result><result cellposition="3-6" label="2"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="4-6"><actiontitle>CHARGE OR REPLACE BATTERY</actiontitle><content6/></action></result></results></testgrp><testgrp cellposition="4-1" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0003"><testtitle>CHECK GTS OPERATION</testtitle><content6><atten4><ptxt>Read the GTS operator's manual before use.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM100000000G4HQ" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="001"/></mlink></ptxt></atten4><test1><ptxt>Connect the GTS to the DLC3.</ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Turn the ignition switch to ON.</ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Turn the GTS on.</ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Check that the GTS and ECUs can communicate with the ignition switch ON.</ptxt></test1><atten4><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>ECUs and sensors are not displayed on the "Communication Bus Check" screen when the GTS cannot communicate with the vehicle.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If communication between the GTS and ECUs is not possible, either the GTS or vehicle has a malfunction.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If communication between the GTS and ECUs is still not possible even when the GTS is connected to another vehicle, the GTS has a malfunction. Perform the self tests described in the GTS operator's manual. (The GTS may be malfunctioning or its battery may be discharged.)</ptxt></item></list1></atten4><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="1"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="4.13in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="2"><ptxt>OK</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="3"><ptxt>NG</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="4-1" label="2"><action actiontype="next" cellposition="5-1" childid="RM1000000025U8F_01_0136"/></result><result cellposition="4-5" label="3"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="5-5"><actiontitle>GO TO Check CAN Communication Connection</actiontitle><content6><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM10000000270P3" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></content6></action></result></results></testgrp><testgrp cellposition="5-1" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0136"><testtitle>BUS INSPECTION (CHECK CONNECTED ECUS AND SENSORS USING GTS)</testtitle><content6><test1><ptxt>Based on the vehicle equipment and specifications, confirm the systems that use CAN communication.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM1000000026926" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Select "CAN Bus Check" from the screen on the GTS.</ptxt><gts-info category="canbus-connect"><title>CAN Bus Check</title><gts-exec function-id="50007"/><app-communication><app-param name="process-mode">0</app-param><app-param name="edit-mode">1</app-param><app-param name="insert-mode">0</app-param><app-param name="function-tab">6</app-param><app-param name="category-div"/><app-param name="category-div-name"/><app-param name="ecu-id"/><app-param name="ecu-name"/><app-param name="gts-order">0</app-param></app-communication></gts-info></test1><test1><ptxt>Observe the screen for approximately 2 minutes to check the ECUs and sensors displayed on the screen.</ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Check for ECUs or sensors with a background color that indicates that they are currently not communicating.</ptxt><atten3><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>A sub bus monitoring ECU outputs DTCs for its respective ECUs and sensors. Identify the malfunctioning ECU or sensor using the output DTCs.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>ECUs or sensors that are not installed to the vehicle will not be displayed. Do not mistake these for ECUs or sensors that are not communicating.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>When using the combo box, it may be possible to select a sub bus from the drop down list that does not have any connected ECUs or sensors. This is not a malfunction and occurs when there is no optional device connected to a sub bus which is monitored by a sub bus monitoring ECU (gateway function equipped ECU).</ptxt></item></list1></atten3><atten4><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>For details on how to read the "CAN Bus Check" screen, refer to Diagnosis System.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PN" label="Seep00002" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If there is an ECU or sensor whose connection status changes intermittently while checking the "CAN Bus Check" screen, there may be an open circuit in one of the wires of a branch line of an ECU or sensor in the bus. If an open occurs in one of the wires of a CAN branch line, it may interfere with the communication of other ECUs or sensors resulting in an incorrect state being displayed.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>The central gateway ECU (network gateway ECU) displays the connection status of ECUs and sensors connected to the central bus on the GTS.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>Sub bus monitoring ECUs display the connection status of ECUs and sensors connected to their respective sub bus on the GTS.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If a CAN commutation DTC is output for an ECU connected to the sub bus, refer to the corresponding diagnostic procedure.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PN" label="Seep00003" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></item></list1></atten4></test1><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="3.30in"/><colspec colname="col2" colwidth="0.83in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Result</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>No ECUs or sensors are displayed as not communicating</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="1"><ptxt>A</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>ECUs or sensors are displayed as not communicating</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="3"><ptxt>B</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="5-1" label="1"><action actiontype="next" cellposition="6-1" childid="RM1000000025U8F_01_0139"/></result><result cellposition="5-4" label="3"><action actiontype="next" cellposition="6-4" childid="RM1000000025U8F_01_0145"/></result></results></testgrp><testgrp cellposition="6-1" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0139"><testtitle>CHECK DTC (HEALTH CHECK)</testtitle><content6><test1><ptxt>Using the GTS, perform Health Check to read current and history DTCs and record them.</ptxt><atten3><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>CAN communication DTCs are output when there is an open or short in any of the communication lines. Any problems with the power source of a corresponding ECU or sensor, or problems in the ECU or sensor itself also cause these DTCs to be output.</ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If a CAN communication line connector is disconnected with the ignition switch ON or ACC, the ECUs of the corresponding system and related systems store a DTC.</ptxt></item></list1></atten3><atten4><ptxt>If an open occurs in just one of the wires of a CAN branch line, DTCs which are not related to malfunctioning parts may be output (DTCs may be displayed randomly), or a message indicating a communication error may be displayed.</ptxt></atten4></test1><test1><ptxt>Read the DTCs using the GTS and record them.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM1000000026924" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></test1><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="2"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="3.30in"/><colspec colname="col2" colwidth="0.83in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Result</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>DTCs are not output.</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="4"><ptxt>A</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Output DTCs are listed in the Diagnostic Trouble Code Chart for CAN Communication System.</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="2"><ptxt>B</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Output DTCs are not listed in the Diagnostic Trouble Code Chart for CAN Communication System.</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="3"><ptxt>C</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="6-1" label="4"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="7-1"><actiontitle>INSPECT FOR INTERMITTENT PROBLEMS</actiontitle><content6><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM1000000025AW3" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></content6></action></result><result cellposition="6-2" label="2"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="7-2"><actiontitle>GO TO DTC CHART</actiontitle><content6><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM1000000026924" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></content6></action></result><result cellposition="6-3" label="3"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="7-3"><actiontitle>GO TO PERFORM DIAGNOSIS FOR RESPECTIVE SYSTEM</actiontitle><content6/></action></result></results></testgrp><testgrp cellposition="6-4" id="RM1000000025U8F_01_0145"><testtitle>CAN BUS INSPECTION (DETERMINE CAUSE OF PROBLEM SYMPTOM)</testtitle><content6><test1><ptxt>Using the GTS, display the "CAN Bus Check" screen again.</ptxt><gts-info category="canbus-connect"><title>CAN Bus Check</title><gts-exec function-id="50007"/><app-communication><app-param name="process-mode">0</app-param><app-param name="edit-mode">1</app-param><app-param name="insert-mode">0</app-param><app-param name="function-tab">6</app-param><app-param name="category-div"/><app-param name="category-div-name"/><app-param name="ecu-id"/><app-param name="ecu-name"/><app-param name="gts-order">0</app-param></app-communication></gts-info></test1><test1><ptxt>Observe the screen for approximately 2 minutes to check the ECUs and sensors displayed on the screen.</ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Disconnect the cable from the negative (-) battery terminal.</ptxt></test1><test1><ptxt>Measure the resistance of the CAN bus for which a malfunction is confirmed from the connector on the central gateway ECU (network gateway ECU) side.</ptxt><atten4><list1 type="unordered"><item><ptxt>For details on the terminal arrangement of the central gateway ECU (network gateway ECU), refer to Terminals of ECU.</ptxt><ptxt>Click here<mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PF" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></item><item><ptxt>If the CAN bus main line is normal and there is an ECU or sensor whose connection status changes intermittently while checking the "Communication Bus Check" screen, there may be an open circuit in one of the wires of a branch line of an ECU or sensor in the bus. If an open occurs in one of the wires of a CAN branch line, it may interfere with the communication of other ECUs or sensors resulting in an incorrect state being displayed.</ptxt><ptxt>Performing the bus inspection again may help in determining the suspected area.</ptxt></item></list1></atten4><spec type="resistance"><title>Standard Resistance</title><table><tgroup cols="3"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="1.39in"/><colspec colname="col2" colwidth="1.39in"/><colspec colname="col3" colwidth="1.35in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Tester Connection</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Condition</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Specified Condition</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>CANH - CANL of a suspected bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Cable disconnected from negative (-) battery terminal</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>54 to 69 Ω</ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>CANH - body ground of a suspected bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Cable disconnected from negative (-) battery terminal</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>200 Ω or higher</ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>CANL - body ground of a suspected bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Cable disconnected from negative (-) battery terminal</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>200 Ω or higher</ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>CANH - +B of a suspected bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Cable disconnected from negative (-) battery terminal</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>6 kΩ or higher</ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>CANL - +B of a suspected bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Cable disconnected from negative (-) battery terminal</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>6 kΩ or higher</ptxt></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></test1><spec type="other"><title>Result</title><table><tgroup cols="1"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="4.13in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Proceed to</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="1"><ptxt>OK</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><judge-value label="2"><ptxt>NG</ptxt></judge-value></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></spec></content6><results><result cellposition="6-4" label="1"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="7-4"><actiontitle>GO TO DIAGNOSIS PROCEDURE FOR RESPECTIVE COMMUNICATION STOP</actiontitle><content6><table pgwide="1"><tgroup cols="4"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="2.48in"/><colspec colname="col2" colwidth="1.06in"/><colspec colname="col3" colwidth="2.48in"/><colspec colname="col4" colwidth="1.06in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>ECU or Sensor Displayed on GTS as Not Communicating</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Link</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>ECU or Sensor Displayed on GTS as Not Communicating</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Link</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Skid Control (ABS/VSC/TRAC)</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266QU" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Spiral cable (Steering Angle Sensor)</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PI" label="Seep00002" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>ECM (Engine)</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PJ" label="Seep00003" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Combination Meter</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PK" label="Seep00004" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Front Radar</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PP" label="Seep00005" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Front Camera Module</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266Q0" label="Seep00006" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry></row><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>Airbag</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266PL" label="Seep00007" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>-</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>-</ptxt></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></content6></action></result><result cellposition="6-5" label="2"><action actiontype="end" cellposition="7-5"><actiontitle>GO TO DIAGNOSIS PROCEDURE FOR RESPECTIVE BUS</actiontitle><content6><table pgwide="1"><tgroup cols="4"><colspec colname="col1" colwidth="2.48in"/><colspec colname="col2" colwidth="1.06in"/><colspec colname="col3" colwidth="2.48in"/><colspec colname="col4" colwidth="1.06in"/><thead><row><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Target Bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Link</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Target Bus</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt>Link</ptxt></entry></row></thead><tbody><row><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>BUS 2</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266ZB" label="Seep00001" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry><entry align="left" valign="middle"><ptxt>BUS 5</ptxt></entry><entry align="center" valign="middle"><ptxt><mlink><xref href="RM10000000266ZC" label="Seep00002" term-id-from="009"/></mlink></ptxt></entry></row></tbody></tgroup></table></content6></action></result></results></testgrp></subpara></para></ttl></section></servcat></pub></tmc-service-paragraph>